let Questions = [
  {
    question: "What is HOC",
    answer: "",
  },

  {
    question: "What are differeces in states and props",
    answer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "What are three phases of life cycle?",
    answer: "Mounting, Updating, Unmounting",
  },
  {
    question: "What are alternatives of Redux",
    answer: "mobx,flux,appollo graphQL",
  },
  {
    question: "What is synthetic event",
    answer:
      "A cross browser wrapper of native events to make sure react events are consistant accross  browser",
  },
  {
    question: "What is ref in react",
    answer: "Reference of a component of single element",
  },
  {
    question: "What are uses of refs?",
    answer:
      "Third party DOM integration,Animations initiation, Media playback, focus",
  },
  {
    question: "What are controlled components",
    answer: "Componnets that have ability to maintain their states",
  },
  {
    question: "What can be done when react component is slow",
    answer:
      "Use pure function, React.usememo uses can be used whereever necessery",
  },
  {
    question: "What are different prop types in react",
    answer: "Func , bool , node , string, number",
  },
  {
    question: "",
    answer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "",
    answer: "",
  },
  {
    question: "",
    answer: "",
  },
];
